Oh my god, check it out. Princess
Celestia is holding a talent competition
for ski resort tickets. Well, yehad.
Now, don't she know Ponyville ski resort
tickets are just $2? Like, that's
cheaper than a fried dill pickle at the
county fair. Oh, let's not be too harsh
on her, ladies. I'm sure she's solely in
it for the love of competition and not
because she's desperate for attention.
Yeah, I heard Twilight felt bad for her,
so she joined the contest just so
Celestia wouldn't feel embarrassed.
>> Thanks for agreeing to this, Fluttershy.
We really needed someone to stand in the
background to make people think we got
babes.
>> Well, I thank you for having me. Would
you mind telling me the song you're
singing now?
>> No.
Hey, Twilight. Since you were the only
ones who entered my contest, you can
just take the tickets if you want and
miss the opportunity of so much fun. No
way, princess. We're going to do this
the right way.
>> Hit it, Fluttershy.
>> Looking kind of sexy. Yeah, I see the
shortest in the corn. They started
breaking down
and then they started getting freaky on
the dance
tonight.
Bring your friend
down. asking girls freaking out freaking
out
if they trying to sex me. I know they
wanted alcoholics got some sex drinks
got me wanting to get messy. So let's
get messy girls. Come on, let's go get
messy. Girl, come on. She know you want
this. The hot collation make you feel
the toxic
Rolex watches Bentley Coops with the 20
wheel spin. I can taste the ice with the
grill in if you want me baby feel me cuz
I don't waste my time with them.
>> That's enough. Fluttershy, shut the
music off. My god.
>> Did we win?
>> Yes, Twilight. You won. Please go take
the tickets and please, for the love of
God, never come back for our sake.
>> We did it, [__] who proved ponies can
sing even better than Michael Jackson.
No, Sparkle. I did it and I crushed it.
I'll go get that.
Daddy, what are you doing here? Triick,
my boy, I've come to apologize to you
for spanking you on the butt so many
times. It's not right for one's old man
to still be spanking him at 59 years
old. Wow, Dad. I never thought you
actually listened to me. Can I have a
hug?
Yeah, I guess.
Are those three men? You're not out with
friends at all. This is just a secret
homosexual gathering. You lied to me.
Everybody run. It's my dad.
Oh my god.
Sparky, run. I'll call the cops.
>> Forget about me. T-Rex's daddy is
getting away.
>> Oh my god, Derek. Like, I cannot believe
you have done this. How could you like
emotionally harm our son like this?
Dude, you know I had to do it to him.
Richard, I caught T-R with other gay
guys. Do you really want him to end up
in the same gay abusive relationship
like us and every other gay person ever?
Dude, Derek, his path is like not for us
to forge. Bro, Triick must make his own
decisions in life, just like I did when
I left my previous romantic relationship
with my father to be with you. But I
realize now that was a mistake because
it led us here on opposite sides of the
law. I cannot believe I ever considered
you my brother. And I can't believe I
once considered you my lover, but here
we are. And now it ends tonight here in
the suburban neighborhood of Ponyville.
And yet, I cannot just throw away my
feelings. Turn around so I don't have to
look you in the eye while I do it.
He was hiding a grenade launcher in his
smelly butt crack.
>> Watch out, T-Rex's other dad. If those
grenades go off, they might be really
stinky.
>> Don't worry, Sparky. Those grenades are
fake. Nobody would put a real grenade in
their butt crack.
Earlier today, authorities responded to
a scene in which two brothers who were
also in a romantic relationship managed
to shoot and kill each other
simultaneously during a dramatic
argument in the rain. Witnesses who were
there said the scene was kind of
bananas.
Yo, that's bananas.
>> Dude, Trixie, watching you hit that ramp
was awesome. I have literally never seen
a pony fart then poop themselves to gain
speed going down the slopes before.
>> Yeah, it's too bad your friend
Fluttershy was below me and got a
mouthful of poopy. But at least it made
for an unforgettable experience.
>> Hey, what are you girls talking about?
Oh, nothing, girl. Did you get our room
keys?
>> Uh, Fluttershy, could you like tell your
lesbian friends to control their stupid
stinky demon child? Like, no cap. She's
like eating our dad's baseball throwing
arm and he's going to be really pissed
off if she starts eating the other. What
is wrong with your friends? Dad, we all
hear you. You don't have to cry like a
baby. Like you will live. Daddy, you're
a big guy.
>> Daddy, what is the problem?
>> Are you blind? The girl that looks like
Coconut Head from Ned's Declassified
just ripped my arm off.
>> Oh, Daddy Kins, it's all because you
keep styling your hair to look like
whipped cream. We kept on telling you
something like this would happen sooner
or later.
>> That's it. I'm going outside for a smoke
and a beer.
All right, dudes. I'm going out there to
kill Twilight now.
>> Bro, isn't it too soon? Do you even have
a plan?
>> Sparky is right, Spike. And isn't
Fluttershy's brother is out there? He
looks really strong and unreasonably hot
with a toned, muscular butt crack. I'm
not sure we can take him. You like what
you see, gay boy?
People often say, "I have quite the
garbage dump on me, so I'm not surprised
you're so taken aback by it." "Hey, fat
guy, here's my number. I'm difficult to
contact, so you will reach me one out of
57 times if you call that number. If you
try to contact me through other means,
you will find I'm impossible to reach."
>> Hey, wait. I I didn't get your name,
dude.
>> Zephr Breeze. But you can call me
breezy, like the cool wind that passes
by your hot butt just after you step out
of a hot tub, only to vanish the very
next second. Just like I am going to
vanish from your life, leaving you
wanting more. I would ask you your name,
but I don't really care.
See that? They're totally going to their
room to make out because everything they
do is gay now. I used to be Twilight's
best friend.
Why is there a caked up Funko Pop
charging right towards us with murderous
intent?
>> Oh, that's just Spike. He's always doing
stupid stuff.
>> Come on. Why can't I pull myself up?
>> It's probably all of that silicone.
Like, bro, I told you your butt lift was
too big. You look like you're smuggling
two beach balls.
>> Dude, Spike, just give up, man. No
shame. Just take the L and go.
You thought you could pull yourself up
with that thing?
>> Like, omg, you really thought this is
why small poopers will always be
superior? You're right, Sparkle. This is
truly a victory for natural butts
everywhere.
>> Spike, jump back over before it's too
late.
Spike, no. We just lost the man with the
biggest butt in the world.
>> Dude, it sucks. His butt may have been
massive, but like his spirit was even
bigger. Even if we can't bring him or
his glorious backside back, we can still
avenge him. But first, I got to give
someone a call.
Like a lovesick puppy you are. Very
well. I'll entertain you for a bit. I
caught you, Breezy.
>> Huh? So, it would seem that you have, or
is it I that caught you in my very own
trap? My lovely little song bird.
>> So, this T-R guy, you're telling me he's
bad news?
>> That's right. And you better stop
interfering with us because if you
don't, you're going to get seriously
hurt. We already lost two of our allies.
>> Oh, that's okay. I'm just like literally
only But I'm not interfering. I'm simply
observing.
>> Well, T Rick just lost his boyfriend to
murder. So, he's going through a rough
time right now. And if you get involved
with him, he just might end up getting
you killed next.
>> Okay. I totally I see what's going on
here then. That gay little queer sees me
as nothing more than a simple
replacement for his lost love. I love
it.
This ski trip just got a whole lot more
interesting.
>> What do you suppose by telling me this
that I'd walk away? Now I find him even
more appealing.
It will be of great joy to break his
little heart for a second time. I've
always wondered what tragedy feels like.
He's going to take a life tonight, isn't
he? You all are. I can feel it. Who's
the victim? I think I deserve to know
since I'll be nearby. watching how you
all fall apart.
Too scared to open your mouth? Then fly
away, little freak, and let me eat my
double stuffed Oreos alone.
>> Twilight, my love, I have a feeling
someone is trying to kill you.
>> The one problem here is the TV isn't
working. Go up and fix the antenna.
>> Trixie is not doing manual labor during
vacation in the midst of a blizzard
sparkle. The lodge workers can see to
that. Well, I guess you just don't love
me then. Don't forget your coat. It's
cold out. Just nag nag nag. That's all
you ever do.
These trash cans remind Trixie of when
she would sleep next to dumpsters and
for only $17 and a box of Cheerios
because she was ugly and lacked
self-confidence.
But you saved me from that life, you
crazy girl.
It was an accident. Don't you raise your
voice at me.
>> There she is. T-Rex, the one who killed
Spike and his glorious booty.
>> Trixie literally has no idea who you
are.
>> Well, soon you will because Spike's
booty was a national treasure for
homosexual men and now it's smeared all
over the bottom of an elevator shaft.
>> Excuse me. I came to fix a wire. The TV
isn't working. And also, my dad is
running around outside screaming without
arms. So, this is a lot for me right
now.
>> I'll give you one chance, Blue Pony.
Step aside and let us go downstairs and
kill Twilight or face our unbridled
wrath.
>> The great and powerful Trixie never
flees from a duel.
>> Hey, that belongs to the Snow Lodge, you
jerk.
>> Don't tell me what to do.
A!
>> She farted out of her butt to propel
herself sideways in a means to dodge my
attack.
>> Trixie Fluttershy over here. We can use
this ski lift to escape.
T- Rick, they're getting away after
them.
This battle is between you and me.
Sparky from generation 5 and tamers 1 2
3 4 5's Ugly Pony OC. Two of the most
hated characters in My Little Pony
history. Our battle shall be legendary.
that strength. It's a form of power that
can only be achieved when you're
fighting for the one you love. I also
fight for a man that had a really big
butt. Unfortunately, he was murdered in
cold blood by a pony named Starlight
Glimmer.
>> I see. Trixie also fights for love. For
the girl she loves and doesn't want to
lose.
>> Then you can understand. There should be
no animosity between those who share the
same feelings. What do you say we end
this foolish battle?
>> You know what you're right. The great
and powerful Trixie accepts your truce.
But only if you walk over here so we can
shake hooves on it.
She was hiding a grenade launcher in her
butt crack. She's using my father's own
technique against me.
It's a good thing my butt saved me from
that fall. Now I can kill Twilight while
she's alone.
Seems like they're not here. Guess
they're out making out somewhere because
they're gay. Hey, is that her phone?
Wow, she looks sort of happy.
Hey, Spike. Oh, good. I didn't expect
you to be alive. Did you kill her yet or
what? Oh, yeah. And T- Rick is dead. I
think it was coconuts. There was blood
everywhere. I didn't even know a body
could hold so much blood. Spike, what's
the matter? Are you good, baby girl?
>> You know, before the main six, I used to
be Twilight's best friend.
>> Yeah, I know. You never shut up about
it.
>> Oh, but over time, things changed. She
moved on. And I guess I never really
did.
>> Spike, dude. We're both 47 years old. We
still have our whole lives ahead of us.
If you want to give up this mission of
revenge, I won't blame you.
>> Trixie told me someone was hunting me,
but I never would have guessed it were
you two stupid dragons.
>> Twilight, it's over. I don't want to
fight with you.
>> No, Spike. I decide when this ends. You
thought you could sneak around with
that, but bouncing all over the place.
Those massive cheeks clapping could be
heard like an atom bomb all throughout
the hotel. You drove T- Rick to his
death because of your own greed and
lust. And now your best friend shall
die, too. It's the only way you will
learn.
>> Let him go. He didn't even do anything.
>> Oh, you want me to spare him? Then I
want you to beg on your knees.
>> Please, please, Twilight. I'm sorry I
ever attacked you. I'm sorry I tried to
kill you. I'm sorry I got a buttlft. I'm
sorry for everything.
>> Wow. Even with you humiliating yourself
like that, Spike, it's still not enough
to make me care.
>> Where did this sudden rush of power come
from?
>> You idiot. When one defeats a dragon in
combat, they absorb all of that dragon's
essence and power. Sparky is weak as
hell now.
>> Oh, that's neat. Clean the blood from
the carpet. If we get a fine tomorrow
for dirtying up the room, I will kill
you next.
>> Twilight, where the hell have you been?
Loca. Oh my god, there's blood on you.
>> It's the other guys.
>> Damn, my wife is a scrapper. Want to hit
the slopes.
Look at that. Playing in the snow and
all that crap with Trixie like some
loves sick puppy. It makes me sick. We
really should not be stalking Twilight
like this. It is immoral and unbecoming
of us growing ladies.
>> Silence from you, Rarity. Everybody
knows you're just our little lackey.
>> Dude, that was so not cool. Why did you
have to go and make her sad like that?
>> She deserved it.
>> No, she didn't. You know what, Pinkie
Pie? I don't want to spy on Twilight
anymore. I'm going to check on Rarity.
>> You'll come back. You always do. You'll
never be anything without me, Rainbow
Dash.
>> Sorry.
>> No. Um, it's okay, Girly Pop. I know you
didn't. Uh, what do you want?
>> I just wanted to check if you're okay
since Pinky basically told you to shut
up and get lost.
>> Well, thank you, darling. It means a lot
to know some pony at this resort sees me
as something more than a fine face. But
shouldn't you be monitoring Twilight
with Pinky? The whole point of this
ridiculous stalker mission was to make
sure she wasn't fraternizing with
Trixie, was it not?
>> Don't remind me. Watching them be all
smiley and happy together makes me want
to puke. But Pinky was being so freaking
mean to you that I couldn't just leave
you alone.
>> Rainbow, that's unusually very sweet of
you.
>> Well, you look really sad when Pinky
picks on you. And honestly, I kind of
hate it. Really? You care that much?
>> Yeah, I I do.
>> Oh my. Rainbow Dash, are you flirting
with me?
>> Yeah, I I guess I am.
>> Oh dear. Oh dear, Rainbow. This is This
is very complicated.
>> Yeah, no kidding. I mean, Pinkiey's
great and all, but lately she's just
been mean.
>> Oh, Rainbow. I don't want my natural
perfection to come between you.
>> You're not. It was going to happen
sooner or later.
Pinky. I mean, compare her with the rest
of her family. They're like gray while
she's totally pink. It's weird. That's
like generational or a loss right there.
She's got no RZ. Like, no cap. What I'm
trying to say is, girl, as a woman, you
mog her.
>> You think I got RZ?
>> Tell me, Rarity. I have to know. Do you
feel anything for me?
>> I'm not certain.
>> You're not hurting anyone. I promise.
Just tell me what you want. I want
>> Are you two making out?
>> Oh, hi Pinky. What up? This isn't what
it looks like.
>> Oh, okay. Cool. I thought you were about
to kiss or something. That would have
been crazy. Anyway, Twilight moved like
2 in, so I need you back on stalking
duty.
Oh dear, just what in Celestia's good
name did I trot myself into?
Girl, where in tarnation have you been?
What's wrong, sugar? The gals didn't go
and stumble upon our scandalously
passionate little love affair we've been
carrying on for two whole years now, did
they? Well, [__] cuz if they did, I'd
have to drag you around back and shoot
you.
>> Now, girl, you think I'd screw that up?
>> Well, with your track record, forgive me
in thinking that you're kind of a stupid
ass [__]
>> Dude, are you serious right now?
>> Well, hello to you too, Cupcake. I
brought you some roses and a glass of
pill for our date tonight. Do I even
want to know what that is? Also, we
never planned on any date.
>> We didn't have to. I know how you feel,
but I wanted to ask you properly first
since things were moving a little too
fast.
You mean that tactical kiss? I only did
that because you wouldn't shut up. I
see. I misread everything. I'm sorry for
bothering you. Enjoy your vacation.
Oh my god. Don't do the sad, slow walk
away. Is it working?
>> The day started off so well.
Began the night, not expecting the
fright of my life. She was perfect from
what I could tell.
How could I not see the danger right in
front of me?
>> I tried to get the waiter's attention by
blinking in Morse code.
>> Why are you blinking so much?
>> I've got something in my eye.
>> Here, let me get it out.
>> No, thank you. I don't want to die.
Mom was blinking at me. Is this cuz your
date is a freak?
>> No.
>> Very good then.
>> Scheme sure is fun. Okay, go in the
kitchen and make me a double grilled
cheese.
>> Trixie, look. It's a letter from Spike.
Dear Twilight, I'm going out into the
bitter cold to freeze to death. Do not
come looking for me. Goodbye forever,
Spike. Haha.
>> Trixie, this is serious. Put down the
peelable gummy banana peelers. No.
>> Well, he's my friend and friends help
each other. I'm going to go out there
and look for him whether you help me or
not.
>> Okay, I won't.
>> Oh, there you are, Spike. My friend, I
have come to save you.
>> Let's face it, Twilight. You don't need
your old pal Spiky Wy anymore. You have
like 20 other friends.
>> That's not true. Yo [__] He low-key
kind of right though.
>> Listen, fart bag. It doesn't matter how
many friends I have because you'll
always be my friend, too. Friends are
like sex, beer, and money. You can never
have enough. And if anyone tells you
otherwise, they're just poopy baby
liars.
>> Damn, I never thought about it that way.
Are you sure she went this way?
>> Every resident of Ponyville has become
accustomed to the scent of each other's
farts.
>> Hey, Twilight. Oh my god, there's blood
on you.
>> It's the other guys.
>> Damn, my wife is a scrapper.
Dude, Twilight, we also found you by
huffing your farts. We need to talk like
now. Celestia sent us over because you
stole the essence of two dragons, which
is like super illegal cause. It's like
drinking 12 Red Bulls. No,
>> you can't just say no to the princess of
the Sun Egg head.
>> No.
>> Did you capture her?
>> Why is Fluttershy here?
>> Twilight thought she was a double agent.
>> Oh, for Celestia's sake, girls. It was
literally one job.
>> You didn't tell us she had dragon
powers.
>> Yes, she did.
>> She did. I'm embarrassed. No, Rainbow
Dash. The one who should be embarrassed
is me. I believed in you and that was my
own mistake. What an absolute fool I
was,
>> princess.
>> No, Rarity. This isn't your failure.
It's mine because I genuinely thought,
"Hey, maybe this time they won't
embarrass me." And like a clown, like an
actual circus pony, I trusted all of
you.
>> Are you going to be okay?
>> No, Fluttershy. I will not be okay. My
star pupil has stolen the powers of
multiple dragons and folded all of you
like a burrito. And now I have to clean
this whole mess up myself because
apparently I am the stupid idiot who
believes in friendship.
>> Hey, Princess Celestia, I have an idea.
Why don't we just go tell Twilight not
to be evil?
>> Go. Spell that gives ponies leukemia.
>> Hey everyone, get your butts over here.
The tree lighting ceremony is going to
start any minute. Spike, look. Tyrex
survived his injuries, too. It's a
Christmas miracle.
>> What do you say, Spike? Want to lay that
few to rest and spend Christmas with our
friends?
Twilight Trixie, I need your help.
Twilight Trixie, I need your help. Stop
copying me. Stop copying me.
>> Twilight, is this like a cloning thing?
Should we be worried?
Back to
mywhere.
>> You know I'm going to have to take away
those newly acquired dragon powers.
>> Cry about it.
>> You're starting to sound like a villain.
>> Yeah, pretty hot, right?
The tree is really pretty. You really
did all of the decorating yourself?
Well, I couldn't have done it without
your help. After all, the lights are
from your bag in the room. That's funny.
It sounded like you said you used the
lights from Trixiey's magic yellow bag,
which aren't actually lights at all, but
fireworks with the bombing power to
level a city block.
>> Yeah, that would be pretty funny.
Tell me things I'll never know.
Still trying to find a way to leave
so I can learn to never go back home.
I got to make it get away. Get away.
Got to let stay. Never stay. Never stay.
What have I got to do? Whatever got
it finally
It up
again.
Heat.
Hey, Dashy. Want to go get hot chocolate
before we head home? Oh, or maybe some
nachos. I love nachos.
>> Pinky girl, I really think we need to
talk.
Holy Jesus. Rainbow Dash said we need to
talk. Those are like the worst words
anyone can hear in any relationship.
>> Dashy, if this is about me knocking
Rarity off the ski lift, we all know she
deserved it. You skanky ass gay
rainbowhaired mother.
>> Pinky, stop. This is serious. If it's
serious, can't you take the drama
outside?
>> Yeah, for real, girl. We all know you
[__] are like super weirdly gay and
stuff. Like everyone on this bus except
for Fluttershy is super gay. Okay, but
it's obvious you're not really
compatible. Aside from Rainbow having
blue fur and pink eyes, and you have
pink eyes and blue fur. Oh my god.
Actually, that is super cute. But like,
really? Go outside and save us from the
shitfest that are your lives.
>> Who invited the random gay guy? All
right, [__] Emma, keep it a stack.
Pink. Uh, mean. Uh, Diane Pie, I'm
breaking up with you.
Pinky, I didn't start dating you because
I loved you. I started dating you
because I felt bad for you since you're
mentally challenged.
>> You're lying to me. Stop it.
>> Rarity, I need to tell you something,
too. I care about you. And because I
care about you, I don't want to screw
things up by jumping into something I'm
not ready for. I realized something
after all this. You can't fall in love
with some pony you're not even friends
with first.
>> A
>> Why are you [__] happy for her? She
just lied about being my friend.
>> Why are you bullying me? I'm right.
>> Are you saying you want to be my friend?
>> Rainbow say no.
>> Yes.
>> That wasn't a no.
>> Friends is where ponies should start.
>> Rainbow. I'd love to be friends. But
where will we end up?
>> I don't know yet. But wherever it is, I
want it to be real.
>> I got to say, Dash, you really dodged a
mighty bullet. Why? I remember when
Pinkie Pie broke into my house just last
night to steal my jar of pickle
jalapenos. Yeehaw!
>> I am so mad. If only there was some way
I could obtain a substantial amount of
power so that I could enact brutal
revenge against my friends.
>> If one defeats a dragon in combat, they
will steal that dragon's essence and
obtain a substantial amount of power.
I did nothing to you. What the
Well, [__] Now, who's this pretty
little angel? Guess I must be in heaven
or some [__] [__]
>> You think I'm pretty? No one's ever
called me that before.
>> Wait, Derpy, the hell is going on here?
You're not an angel. And why are you
dressed as a pirate?
>> I went to Burger King to buy the new
Bikini Bottom bundle. Why didn't you
tell me you were alive?
>> Well, [__] Derpy. I think it's time I
finally be honest with you. After you
punched me in the face like a [__] I
actually survived that fall.
>> Okay.
[__] can you let me talk?
>> Sorry. My therapist says I should make
sure to let the other pony know. I'm
listening since sometimes they might not
notice because my eyes go two different
ways.
>> Okay. Well, as I was saying before, the
only thing that fueled me forward was my
hatred for you since you punched me in
the face. So, I joined up with Spike and
Sparky so that one day I could return
the favor. Yeah, I heard everything
already.
>> You did,
>> Sparky. The dragon was arrested earlier
today when his friends discovered he
wasn't actually a baby dragon, but in
fact, a 47year-old man only acting like
a baby dragon to get free financial
benefits for dragon babies.
But that isn't important, Bulk. Why
didn't you just tell me you were mad
that I made you drop from the window of
a 50story penthouse causing you to fall
to your presumed death? I would have
apologized or something.
>> Yeah, I guess you're right. I wouldn't
blame you if you hate me.
>> If I hated you, would I have brought you
the bikini bottom meal from Burger
King's limited time Spongebob
Squarepants collaboration menu?
>> Oh my god, I freaking love Spongebob.
Oh my god, me too. My husband thinks
it's for babies, so I have to watch it
in secret.
>> Damn, he sounds like a [__]
>> He hits me, so I don't like to talk
about him.
>> Okay, I'm going to eat these cheesy
bacon potato bites.
>> Hey, Bulk. It's still Christmas, you
know. Maybe we could get you discharged
from the hospital and we can go back to
my place and watch a very Jonas
Christmas before my husband gets off
work.
Yeah, you know what? That sounds sort of
fun. Let's go.